Okay, Jessica, keep it together.
You got this!
Hal needed an off-road vacay,
and you're a Green Lantern.
He asked you to cover his shift
at the Hall of Justice, no biggie.
You are calm, collected, and in control.
Calm, collected, and in control, hmm?
Shush, you! I don't remember
Hal's Ring talking back to him.
That's because Green Lantern Jordan
had accumulated enough Lantern points
to unlock the mute button.
Ring, enable mute.
You, however,
Green Lantern Jessica Cruz, have not!
- Looks like trouble.
- Oh, hi, Justice League.
Uh, I didn't touch it.
I mean, I was going to touch it,
but I didn't touch it,
so it isn't my fault, I swear!
And everyone is looking at me,
and I should shut up now!
- Minus five Lantern points.
- What for?
- Don't make excuses.
- Not to worry, Green Lantern.
You didn't do anything wrong.
This is the trouble alert.
- It alerts us when...
- When there's trouble?
Yes, see? You're a natural at this.
Breaking News with Lois Lane live.
It seems trouble is exactly what we've got.
And it starts with a capital "L."
Well, Lois is many things, Batman,
but I wouldn't call her trouble.
Not Lois, Superman. Look!
This is Lois Lane
reporting from Area 52 at Dread Lake,
where the intergalactic bounty hunter
known as Lobo is on a rampage.
This is like looking for a Denebian needle
in an Alterian haystack creature.
The now-defunct Area 52 facility
was an attempt to streamline
the military's overly complex
secret alien technology department.
Defunct? I thought
they just built that thing.
The simplification program
made things much more complicated.
They moved everything
to a warehouse in Rebirth, New Jersey.
Where are you, you little
Denebian slime bender? Yeah!
Lobo, a Czarnian who is
super strong, super tough,
and has a super potty mouth,
appears to be in search of something.
There's no telling what
dangerous artifact Lobo will discover.
We need to get to Dread Lake fast.
Did someone say "Lake"?
Why, that sounds like a job for Aquaman!
Aquaman, you should know that
Dread Lake isn't really your...
Whoa. Sorry. Reception
down here is a little spotty.
I'll see you there. Aquaman out!
Evidently, he did not get my memo
about building an undersea cell tower.
We really should build
an undersea cell tower down here.
The reception is horrible, Orm.
I told you, brother,
I prefer to be called "Ocean Master".
Oh, sorry, Ocean Master.
Don't worry, I'll call you whatever you want.
Oh. There she is. The Aquajet!
We just detailed it for you, sire.
And a wonderful job you did, too.
You guys are great.
I love being the king of you.
I almost feel bad about taking it
up to the dusty old surface world.
No, no, no. Go! You're needed up there.
I'll take care of everything
down here while you're gone. Again.
Aw.
Thanks, Ormi!
- It's "Ocean Master".
- Right. Right, right.
Although, kind of a weird nickname,
seeing as I am
the King of the Seven Seas and all.
But, uh, whatever.
I'm just glad
we can move beyond our petty squabbles,
and work to help Atlantis, nay, the world!
Together!
Yes, I love being a team player.
Tell Mera I'll be home for dinner.
It's great to be King.
Is it? We'll soon see.
What? Get back to work!
All right, Aquajet, we're freshwater bound.
It's so gratifying
when my friends in the Justice League
have a water-based problem
and they need my help.
Where are you?
You can't hide from the Main Man forever!
Yeah!
- Okay, Jimmy. On me.
- Lois? Is this a good idea?
Pulitzers were never won
with good ideas, Jimmy.
Now, come on.
Uh, isn't that the only reason
they're awarded?
Lobo! Lois Lane
reporting for the Daily Planet.
Argh! Paparazzi!
No, I'm a serious journalist.
If I were paparazzi, I'd have to criticize
your atrocious fashion choices.
- So 1983.
- What?
Lady, the Main Man always says,
"Black is the new black!"
Well, I say, the Main Man
is about to be feeling the pain, man!
- Says who?
- Says the Justice League!
Jimmy, duck!
Pleasure to meet you, Lobo.
I am Aquaman, Master of the Seven Seas,
defender of dolphins, King of Atlantis.
- Wrecker of jets!
- Wrecker of...
Uh, I am unfamiliar with that moniker.
Let me fix that!
So long, you Fluvian seaweed farmer!
No, don't do that! Those are critical.
Hey! This is a custom-built vehicle,
and it was just waxed!
It seems that Aquaman inexplicably is
the first of the Justice League to arrive.
Despite the fact that we are in the desert.
Uh, farewell, mighty Aquajet,
you've served your King well!
Aquaman! Lois Lane of the Daily Planet.
It looks like you really,
as we professional journalists say,
"Got your tail fin handed to you"
by the Main Man, Lobo!
No need to worry, Miss Lane.
I'll just call for backup,
using my aqua-telepathic powers
to summon my fellow water creatures,
here at Dread Lake.
But Dread Lake is a dry lake bed!
Well, that would be
challenging then, wouldn't it?
So much for plan A, B, and C.
No matter, I am still really strong.
And... Huh?
Ow! Jeez!
That's gotta hurt!
Good golly, Miss Lane. Aquaman
is really getting filleted out there!
Not in the face, not in the face!
Get out of here!
Help!
This is no way to treat royalty!
Yeah! A royal pain in the bleezors!
This is why you never send a fish
to do a man's job.
- Jimmy, tell me you're getting this.
- Every frame.
But what happens when Lobo gets us?
Don't panic, Jimmy.
Here comes the Justice League!
It's hero time!
You want me to hero now, really?
In front of the whole Justice League?
With everyone watching?
Come on, Green Lantern. Or you'll miss
our stylish superhero landing.
Oh! Who would wanna miss that?
- Jimmy! Slow-mo hero entrance.
- Ooh, right!
Still plenty of time to get the best part!
Give yourself up now, Lobo.
You may be strong where you come from,
but the yellow sun of Earth
makes me the strongest...
Give up? The Main Man don't give up ever!
I actually felt that!
We might need some help.
Ah! I'll be out of here in a trice!
Lobo is as strong as Superman?
- Great!
- You got that right, Tin Man!
You're gonna have to try harder
to put down the Main Man.
Maybe Batman can stop him with something
from his cute little tool belt thingy.
Oh, no, she didn't.
Ha!
What? You know, his little belt of bags.
It's adorable.
You mean my Utility Belt!
It's a convenient storage space
for an assortment of tools
without them getting in the way!
Would a cute little belt thingy do that?
Uh, kinda.
- Maybe.
- You be you, Batman.
- I'm sorry. I just thought...
- Focus!
If we want to succeed,
we'll have to work together.
Everyone, on the count of three. One...
Um, well, don't wait for me!
- Two...
- Don't screw this up.
Gotta make something big, strong.
Three!
A safe? Argh!
Oh, how brave. Minus one point.
Ha! Child's play!
Hey! Keep kicking those flippers,
Mr. Jellyfish!
Uh, Jellyfish don't actually have flippers.
Mind if I take you for a spin?
Superman, Cyborg, now!
Hey. Ah! So, this is where
you've been hiding?
Come to Papa!
- The show is over, right?
- It better be.
We hit him with everything we've got!
If that's all you've got,
you better get more.
Impossible. There's not a scratch on him!
Lantern, hit him with everything you've got.
Uh, okay.
I did it!
I didn't do it.
I'd love to stay and play,
but I've got what I came for.
So long, Justice Losers!
Quick! Before he gets away!
Yeah!
- Good riddance.
- What do you think he was here for?
I don't know.
But whatever it is, it can't be good.
Um. Anyone seen Aquaman?
- A little help, please!
- Don't worry. I'll save you!
Thanks, team. I'm glad you showed up.
We really saved the day.
Am I right?
- Lois Lane, Daily Planet.
- Yes, I am aware.
How does it feel to have
been humiliated by Lobo,
and saved, once again, by the Justice League?
Well, I'm part of a team.
A win for us all is a win for me.
So, you don't mind that the world watched
the King of Atlantis
run away from Lobo like a scared fish?
No, that's
an unfair characterization of fish.
- And, uh, I didn't run.
- Lois, if I may?
Aquaman is an essential member
of the Justice League.
- In what way?
- Now, well, he... Uh...
- He, uh...
- Don't look at me. I just got here.
Aquaman's ability to talk to sea life
is a critical skill.
One that I'm sure
he'll use with great effectiveness,
sometime in the future,
when it becomes necessary.
There you have it, ladies and gentlemen.
Aquaman's teammates
are 100% supportive of him,
despite his overly specialized powers.
For the Daily Planet,
Lois Lane is signing off.
Cut! Great stuff. Let's get back home
and run this on tonight's seven o'clock.
I wouldn't worry about it, Aquaman.
Not many people watch network news anymore.
Oh, I'm not worried.
Besides, we don't get cable in Atlantis.
I'm just excited we're finally all together.
How about we go somewhere
to feast and celebrate?
Or, or... Or we figure out
why Lobo was here in the first place.
Nothing says celebration like apple pie.
I can make you an ambrosia to make
the gods weep!
Let's hit Big Belly Burger!
Allow me to cordially
invite you all to Atlantis!
Where we shall celebrate my anniversary
as King of the Seven Seas!
We're going to Atlantis. That is so awesome!
Road trip under the sea! I love the sea!
Friendly fishies, peaceful porpoises.
No one watching you!
Plus five for appropriate
construct building. Bravo!
Ah, the ocean.
Home to the most interesting
forms of life known to man.
Outside of you guys, I mean.
Oh! Fishies!
Yes, fish, plants.
We have everything down here.
Even froyo?
Well, no, that melts in the seawater,
but we have colorful rocks.
And, uh, uh... Coral! We have coral.
Aren't coral and rocks the same thing?
Hardly.
Is it me, or is the water changing color?
Good observation, Cyborg.
Red and yellow wavelengths of light
can only travel so far underwater,
which is why everything
looks blue and green at these depths.
Oh, that lack of solar energy
is making me feel a little green.
I've got the cure for
your super seasickness here in Atlantis!
Beautiful.
What's that noise?
Oh, sorry, it sounds like singing.
Oh, that must be my song of arrival.
My people always like to sing
a little ditty when I'm returning home.
Atlanteans really are the nicest people
on the planet. Shh. Listen.
Our King, the King of the Seven Seas
The mightiest hero is he!
He fights and swims, he swims and fights
No greater a hero you'll see!
A shark, a whale, a gale
No! The mightiest hero is he
He fights and swims, he swims and fights
The King of the ocean is he!
- They really love you, Aquaman.
- What's not to love?
Who's that guy? Looks important.
King Poseidon.
In his hand is the mystical Trident of Hope.
Legend states that whosoever pulls
the Trident from the statue's hand,
is the rightful ruler of Atlantis.
- Just like Excalibur!
- "Ex" what now?
Has anyone been able to do it?
No, it's just an old wives' tale,
although the younglings can be seen
trying to pull it out from time to time.
Look.
- I almost got it. Mine!
- You got it. You've got it.
And here we are!
Uh, question. How are we gonna
breathe down here?
I've developed a special Bat aqua spray
that will temporarily enable us
to oxygenate the water around us.
Oh, you keep a mist spray
in those cute little pouches?
Welcome! Please make yourselves at home.
As my dolphin friends
from the Gulf of Mexico say...
Roughly translated, mi casa es su casa.
Arthur, you've finally returned.
Mera, so great to see you!
- Who's that tall glass of water?
- Tall?
Aren't we all the same size, Cyborg?
This is my wife, Mera.
Wait, you're married?
I mean, of course, you're married.
Aquaman talks about you all the time.
Well, I'm sorry I haven't had a chance
to meet you all in person.
I've been busy perfecting my craft
while Arthur has been away.
- Your craft?
- Yes.
Not only is Mera the Queen of Atlantis,
she's also a master conjuror of hard water.
- Oh! Make the fish!
- Hard water?
- Is that like hard candy?
- Oh, no, no. It's better.
Watch this. Mera, make the fish!
Isn't that amazing?
Oh, my God! How did you do that?
Magic. With my aquakinesis,
I can make anything.
- Here's a car.
- Make the fish again!
- And a chair.
- The fish!
And here's your fish again, Arthur.
Fish! That kills me every time.
I am so glad you are here.
And just in time
for the royal feast in honor of Arthur.
Please, won't you join me
at the banquet in the throne room?
Yes!
Grub time! Time to put
my cast iron stomach to the test.
Throne room? You sit on a throne?
Ha! It's just a small one.
Oh, man,
I bet they have the best seafood here!
Right you are, Cyborg.
Atlantis is the culinary epicenter
of the ocean.
I'm sure you'll enjoy it.
Tonight, we'll be having
your choice of seaweed burgers,
seaweed spaghetti or seaweed salad.
Seaweed? What about lobster, or crab?
Or maybe even some shrimp?
Heavens no!
Under the sea, all sea life
have full citizenship rights.
But don't worry, try the seaweed slaw.
It is num-num nummy in your tum-tum tummy.
Oh, man! I was really
looking forward to some lobster!
My bad.
Does anyone else hear that?
Or do I have another bad
case of super swimmers' ear?
Bat burp. Pardon. It's coming from outside.
Gather round, gather round! Closer, closer!
- This is really too much!
- How long is this going to go on?
Maybe he'll blow our minds
this time with something.
Last time, he talked for three hours.
I've got ships to wax!
I've come to discuss
a matter of grave importance.
The fate of Atlantis!
- Ocean Master.
- Who is Ocean Master?
Only the saltiest scoundrel
of the Seven Seas.
He's also my half-brother.
Once you get to know him,
he's really not that bad. Come on!
Ocean Master is related to Aquaman?
I don't recall him sharing that
on his application form.
Now I'll have to update his records.
You say that our King is mighty,
but on the surface world,
he's referred to as a joke!
The only joke I see around here
is up on stage!
Really? Let me ask you.
If the king can't defeat
a surface dweller up there,
how is he going to defend you down here, hmm?
I don't know. He's always
treated us pretty well.
Has he?
Please let me shed some light
on our beloved King.
Warning!
Argh!
Green Lantern, what are you doing?
The Ring just did this on its own.
Detecting increasing levels of rage.
What was that? What's going on?
As I was saying about our absent King...
Absent King...
How can you follow a king
that everyone laughs at? Behold!
Coward! Ran away!
Coward?
I was stalling until
the Justice League showed up!
And lastly, how can you trust a king
that is actually only
half-Atlantean to begin with?
Well yeah, my father was an average
run-of-the-mill surface dweller.
I have to update the files again!
- He can't be King!
- Argh! This changes everything.
Ocean Master, brother,
what is the meaning of this?
Is this payback for the time
I locked you in that bathroom?
Let's go inside and talk.
Enough talking! It's time for action!
Too long have you broken
the laws of Atlantis!
Laws? Arthur, what is he talking about?
I'll show you.
You aren't actually supposed to be King.
Behold! The Constitution of Atlantis.
- What does that prove?
- There, near the bottom, in fine print.
Here, let me use my super vision.
Wow! That... That is small.
I might need a magnifying glass.
Yet another advantage of my Utility Belt.
Let's see. It says,
"To rule Atlantis,
you must be full-blooded Atlantean."
Oh, no!
I can't breathe!
But you can breathe anywhere.
Oh. Good point.
So, you see, my brother,
you aren't the rightful ruler.
I am!
Ocean Master! Ocean Master!
Arthur, what are you going to do?
There is only one thing I can do.
In accordance with the Atlantean law
I have sworn to uphold,
I hereby relinquish my crown to my brother.
Half-brother.
Rule well, my King.
No takesie-backsies.
Ocean Master! Ocean Master! Ocean Master!
Arthur! I can't believe you
just gave your throne away.
Mera, I have made my decision.
Without even talking to me about it?
We're supposed to be a team, Arthur.
- Mera, I...
- No.
This is what you want, fine.
You can do it without me!
Wow! What a really great trick!
She is really good.
Too soon? My bad.
Now that I am King of Atlantis,
let me introduce you to the person
who encouraged me to take what was mine.
Threat alert! Omega detected!
Oh, no!
My royal adviser,
and all-around good guy, Atrocitus!
Atrocitus!
Execute defense maneuver. Omega five.
This is your defense?
A couch ain't gonna do nothing!
Argh!
Who is Atrocitus?
Atrocitus, leader of the Red Lantern Corps.
They have the ability to enslave minds
with the power of rage.
I suggest leaving, quickly.
Hal spoke of the Red Lanterns.
It's their lantern light that's
infecting the Atlanteans with rage.
Looks like Green Lantern's shield
is protecting us from the red light.
Hello, water-dwellers.
As your new royal adviser,
my first piece of advice is,
destroy the Justice League!
- Destroy them!
- Get them! Get them!
I got the one with the cape!
Get out of that!
I'm not sure how much
more my bubble can take.
Very little.
It somehow doesn't feel right
to just start punching them.
We cannot. I may not be their king,
but they are still my people.
We must retreat and form a plan.
I know a way out, but we need a distraction.
Well, lucky for you, my super useful
Utility Belt has just the thing.
An ink bomb! Ingenious.
Did you see where they went?
Where did they go?
Find them! They couldn't have gotten far!
You've done well, Ocean Master.
You mean "King Ocean Master."
Yes, of course, Your Majesty.
My plan to infect the Atlanteans
with my Red Lantern rage
seems to have worked.
At last, all of Atlantis bows to me!
And now begins Stage Two.
These secret tunnels
are only known to the royal family.
If we act quickly, we might
be able to get out before they stop us.
How? I'm sure they have
the palace surrounded.
- The Sea Gate, of course.
- The "Sea" what now?
Behold!
What is that?
That is the Sea Gate.
It can open an interdimensional portal
between Atlantis and other aquatic
planets throughout the universe!
Oh, I wasn't aware that
Atlantean technology was so advanced.
Updating files.
I think they're down here!
Aquaman, there must be something you can do.
Well, I don't know
how to change the location,
but I can access the last place it opened to.
- Let's move, team.
- You go! I'll stay to close the Gate.
I can't leave my people
in this dire predicament, and Mera!
If you don't come now,
you won't have a people to save.
Jessica, hurry! They're coming.
But where does it lead? What if
there are more people on the other side,
with expectations and judgments?
The odds on that are about
1.7 billion to one.
So, you're saying there's a chance?
Lantern, there's no time for what ifs! Hurry!
There they are!
Wait, don't!
I said "don't," not "donut"!
Minus five Lantern points for poor diction!
They've escaped! Inform Atrocitus!
- Down here!
Threat approaching!
I think I heard something.
Thanks a lot, big mouth!
Quick, run away from your problems.
It seems to help.
A dead end! Oh, no! What am I going to do?
Yes, if only you had the universe's
most powerful weapon in your...
Oh, wait...
Come on, Ring, how about a little help here?
You must overcome your fear.
- I can't!
- You can!
My record for selecting recruits
has been perfect. Until now, anyway.
Well, better luck with the next candidate!
Whoa!
Nailed it!
On the run from my own kingdom.
- Outrageous.
- Where are we?
It looks like some sort of factory.
But what are they making?
And more importantly, where is Green Lantern?
Unfortunately, this crisis
proved too much for her inexperience.
She's a bit too green.
We'll have to go back and get her.
Aquaman, can you turn the Sea Gate back on?
Turn it back on?
Someone's coming. Everyone, hide.
Well, that's strange.
I should have heard them approaching.
- Invasion?
- What's that, Aquaman?
Well, Wonder Woman,
I communicate with aquatic life fluidly,
but I also speak a little cat.
They're readying for an invasion,
or something about kitty litter.
- It could go either way.
- Of course.
That's Dex-Starr, the Red Lantern cat.
It's all so clear now.
Atrocitus and Ocean Master
are using the Sea Gate in Atlantis
to bring an armada
of rage-fueled battle machines to Earth.
Impossible! The Sea Gate isn't designed
to be able to transport an army!
That will take more power than
is available to... Well, anyone.
Speaking of power,
I'm detecting a huge energy surge
coming from somewhere in this room.
- Like that one!
- The orb from Area 52.
That's what's powering the Gate!
Now, Atrocitus can use Atlantis as
a beachhead to attack the surface world.
Ingenious! They've taken my crown,
my kingdom,
and now, the peace I've maintained
between the two realms I call home.
I must get back there!
We're not getting anywhere with all these
robots between us and the Sea Gate.
This looks like a job for Superman!
I don't understand. My powers, they're gone!
Worry about that later, Superman.
Here they come.
Yet another handy tool from
my all-purpose Utility Belt.
Oh.
They must have some automated repair system.
Cyborg, can you disrupt them?
Hold on to your ears. It's sonic cannon time!
Oh, man!
By the hairballs of Hades,
that is one furious feline!
Okay, Clark, you've got this!
Wonder Woman, are you all right?
But, Mother,
all the other kids' jets are visible!
Apparently, Wonder Woman
has been knocked silly.
- Are you sure?
- Bi-ba-ba-ba-ba!
Yeah, I'm sure.
Oh. Hello there.
You're a space dolphin, aren't you?
Yes, I know of your species.
Let me use my telepathic abilities
to ask you for help.
What? I would
never say something about your mother!
My telepathy must not be working
on dolphins from space.
That is one angry space dolphin.
We're completely outmatched.
- We have to get out of here.
- Leave that to me.
This should buy us some time.
- Amazing!
- In here!
Ha! Looks like you can't get in here!
- Nyeh, nyeh...
- Haha. Right. Why is he smiling?
Whoa! Is anyone else hot in here?
I thought it was just me. I'm burning up!
Burned up...
That's why this room is decorated
exactly like the inside of a furnace...
Because it is a furnace!
A furnace! What are we gonna do?
We need to get out of here fast!
Without my powers,
I can't fly us out of here.
And my rocket boots are still waterlogged.
My head is beginning to clear.
All I have to do is...
It appears my grapple
can't reach the top of the smokestack.
I love cheese, but it doesn't love me.
Yeah. Anyways, we just
have to be like jellyfish.
Batman, you don't happen to have a Bat
parachute in your Utility Belt, do you?
There, it's simple.
Heat rises and with it, so should we.
- It's working.
- But not enough. Look!
I don't know if we're gonna make it!
We made it! Hey!
Didn't you say the Sea Gate
went to other water-covered worlds?
It's supposed to.
It feels almost as hot out here as in there.
Where have I led us now? Death Valley?
Nowhere near that close.
Look! A red sun!
No wonder my powers don't work.
We're on a different planet.
We aren't gonna last long out here
without finding civilization.
How did you fit that
and the parachute in your belt?
Bat secret. Now, come on!
I am so getting
a Utility Belt when I get home.
Mera, thank goodness! How did you find me?
I heard your voice coming through
the other side of the tunnel.
And look what I found!
Someone has secretly assembled
an entire armada in my kingdom.
There's enough stuff here for Atrocitus
to take over the surface world.
- We have to tell everyone.
- Why should we?
The surface world
has caused us nothing but trouble.
- They deserve destruction.
- But Aquaman said...
My husband? He's not even
brave enough to fight for his own crown!
Perhaps try talking some sense into her?
Mera, you have to fight it!
I'd rather fight you!
A tactical retreat would be strongly advised.
Maybe you surface-dwellers
should be destroyed.
Starting with you!
Don't! I mean, stay back!
You think the Queen of Atlantis is going
to be afraid of the chicken of the sea?
Ha! You missed!
I wasn't aiming for you.
Argh! Argh!
Plus 10 for ingenuity.
Let's hope those flying lessons
from Hal paid off!
Hey, guys, is it just me,
or is this sand really soft?
It's like we're walking on water. Yes, water!
Water! Look, water!
Come on in, guys! The water is perfect!
It's happening faster than I thought.
The lack of water
is causing him to hallucinate.
I don't feel so good.
Step back.
Let me use some of my Bat
smelling salts to try and revive him.
Your Utility Belt is almost
as great as you are.
Almost. Now, stand back.
He's stiff as a board.
Even if I had my super strength,
I don't think I could move him.
Let me try.
Interesting.
- Interesting how?
- Wonder Woman, can you lift him?
Strange, it's as if his body
is pulling towards something.
If I had to guess,
I think his Atlantean physiology
draws him naturally to water.
He is a human divining rod.
So, what should we do?
Follow his lead.
Ah, Mera.
Rah! Rah! Back off, tadpoles!
I'm the Queen of Atlantis!
The former Queen.
Oh. About that collateral
dethroning, sorry. Not sorry.
But now, that you've seen
the light of my leadership,
how do you wish to serve me, hmm?
Those surface dwellers,
they really rub my scales the wrong way.
- I'm glad to hear it.
- If I may, My Liege?
We have a perfect position in Stage Two.
As per our mutually beneficial arrangement.
Go! Take the surface world
for your new master!
The surface world
and Aquaman will feel my rage!
- I love Star City Pier.
- More than you love me?
Mmm.
- Isn't this fun, Damian?
- Eh.
Oh, come on! It can't be that bad!
Barbara, all we're doing is
going around in a circle.
I'm not sure what's so exhilarating about it.
This is why we took the day off
from being Batgirl and Robin.
You need to learn what it's like
to be a normal kid.
I'm a normal kid. I do kid things.
Like what? You don't play video games,
stay up late past your bedtime.
You don't even talk like a kid.
- Do, too!
- Do not! What are you doing?
Accessing Bat database.
Searching "kid behavior."
Speed reading, and done!
You want me to act like a kid, you got it!
Totes legit and killin' it.
- Huh?
- Take a chill pill, B.
This is gonna be G to the double-O D.
Oh, what have I done?
Selfie!
Shiver me timbers! I've caught one already!
Now, what kind of fish is that?
Wonder what it tastes like fried.
It tastes like rage!
Looks like our day off just got called off.
Robin? Are you listening to me?
- Kids don't listen.
- Argh! Come on!
Hang in there, gang.
We'll take a break
once we get to the top of this ridge.
Oh, no! I'm starting to hallucinate.
You're not hallucinating, Superman.
I see it, too.
That's a funny name for a place.
You think we should go in and take a look?
Whoa!
Wonder Woman!
Ooh!
- What can I get you?
- Five waters, please.
Five waters? You guys
sure ain't from around here.
Let me see what I can pull up for you.
- Ah!
- Oh, yeah!
Sweet singing seahorses! That is
the best water I have ever tasted!
- I'll have another.
- Big spender.
- That's expensive stuff!
- Water is expensive?
Ever since the red guy
sucked all the water up. Oh!
Atrocitus was here?
If he took all the water
from this planet, then...
He might do the same to Earth!
We have to get back home and stop him!
Say, how you people
paying for this here water?
Uh...
Put it on my Batster card.
No credit. Klagthorps only!
What's a Klagthorp?
Sir, there has to be something we can
do around here to pay off our tab.
The only thing you can do is pay up, or else!
Or else what? I've lost everything.
My wife is mad at me,
the world thinks I'm a laughingstock!
You and I could be pals! To pals!
Huh?
- Is Aquaman okay?
- Aquaman is clearly dehydrated.
The lack of water in his system
is obviously affecting his temperament.
You are affecting my temperament, Batman!
All of you are!
Deadbeats, huh?
Well, I guess that means I have
to introduce you to my debt collectors!
Aquaman, look...
No, the only cure for a pity party
is to invite a little company over.
Oh, right. Wait. Huh?
You know, there was a time when
I could have paid for all this water.
Heck! I could have bought
this entire place, but no!
I had to go and give up my crown!
I just bowed and let Ocean Master
take the crown right off my head!
I mean, being a king
is a lot of pressure, you know?
And believe me, at eight tons per
square inch at the bottom of the sea,
I know pressure. I used to be King.
What's going on?
It appears the locals
are paying our tab.
All right!
Gee, Aquaman, that was great!
I mean, is there anything you can't do?
Yodel.
Something to do with how my gills
interact with my uvula.
Give it up for the Main Man!
Uh-oh.
How do I stop this thing?
- Step one. Stop screaming!
- Oh, great!
Ow! Ow! Ow!
Any landing you walk away from... Right?
Correct. Plus two Lantern points
for survival.
Only two? Sheesh!
Green Lantern?
Batgirl? Robin? What are you doing here?
Five points for the kid.
Zero for the old bat!
We were hoping for a day off.
But now,
Aquaman's Atlantean army is attacking?
What? No, no!
The Atlanteans are being controlled
by Atrocitus and his rage light.
We gotta get out of here
and find some other heroes.
There's no time. Look!
Destroy the surface dwellers! Attack! Attack!
Uh-oh.
Well, look what we have here.
Last time I saw you,
I made your friend here
look like a real billinbore.
Easiest money I ever made.
Money? Someone hired you to do that?
Yeah. Some guy named Puddle Prince,
or Lake Leader...
Ocean Master!
Yeah, that's the guy.
He asked me to grab some power orb
and humiliate Salty Britches here
in the process.
The orb that powered
the Red Lantern's Sea Gate.
Well, it doesn't matter if you were
hired or not. Theft is theft.
I'm afraid we're gonna have to take you in.
Whoa. Don't get your blankie in a twist.
I'm not here for a scuffle.
I'm looking for my friend, Fishy.
You wouldn't by chance have
seen my friend, would you?
I recognize him.
And I know where he is.
Then you're gonna tell me right now.
On one condition.
Are you crazy right now? Tell him!
The only condition is,
if you don't tell me,
I'm gonna pound you into minced fish.
Go ahead. I've got nothing else to lose.
But you'll never find out
where your pal Fishy is.
Mmm.
Mr. Jellyfish has a spine after all.
What do you want?
We want you to take us
to the Red Lantern factory
and figure out how to use
the Sea Gate to get us home.
That's the deal. Take it, or leave it.
Fine.
Deal.
Ew!
It looks like the King of Atlantis
has returned.
Bartender, I'll take one more water
for the road.
Sorry, pal. You guys drank the last of it.
Last of it? Don't be ridiculous.
I'm a human divining rod,
and I know where water is.
Why, there's a whole reservoir
right below your bar!
All right. Let's go.
I only have room on my bike
for one more person.
How are the rest of you gonna get there?
I have an idea.
This is awesome!
- It feels like I can fly again!
- Smoother than my invisible jet.
It is mildly amusing.
Bat flip!
The invasion is going swimmingly.
Mouth-breathers have finally run out of air,
as Atlantean ships give
them a taste of their own pollution!
Nothing can stop us,
as we rage against the 29% of the Earth
that hordes 100% of our resources!
Poseidonspeed, friends!
Bring us back a whopper
to hang above the throne!
I love this show!
Now, to begin Stage Three.
Wait, we only talked about two stages.
- Is Stage Three...
- Oh. Didn't I tell you?
I'm using the Atlanteans
to help me assemble a new weapon,
one that will quell
any resistance on the surface world.
Ooh! That sounds really neat.
What does it do?
You'll see soon enough.
Besides, the king needn't bother
with the affairs on the surface.
Ah. That is the deal we made.
I rule everything underwater,
while you handle everything on dry land.
- All right. Carry on.
- As you wish.
Just as we promised, Mr. Lobo.
There's your friend.
Fishy!
So much for the element of surprise.
- Attack for justice!
- Wait for me!
Is there a ladder, or... Ooh! Good.
Get back here, you tin boxes!
Factory robot? Try unsatisfactory robot!
You make me wish I was a dog person.
Fishy! I was so worried about you!
You disappeared,
and I didn't know where you went.
The orb must be powering the entire facility.
Hurry! The Gate is closing.
All right, I'm here! For justice...
Uh, and the Gate is closed.
I can't believe Fishy did that.
He poked me in the eye.
- And hit you with his tail.
- And hit me with his tail!
Not helping, Cyborg.
Listen. Listen...
Friendship, like anything worth having,
is worth fighting for.
Come with us. Help us free Fishy
and the rest of those
under the Red Lantern's control.
No! No!
The Main Man ain't gonna crawl back
and beg to be anyone's friend.
- But...
- No! This is your fight.
I'm done! I don't need any friends!
I don't need anything!
I did not see that coming.
We have to get home to fight Atrocitus' army.
But how?
Hmm. I've got an idea!
Hey, my hot dogs! Oh!
Whoa!
Us against the establishment!
Fight the power!
I love the enthusiasm!
Fly swatter!
I know. I know. It's not a fly swatter.
Quit judging me!
This is Lois Lane, reporting live.
With the rest of
the Justice League still missing,
the only defense against this invasion
are Robin, Batgirl,
and the new Green Lantern!
The whole world is now watching
to see if they can pull it off!
The whole world, watching... This is crazy.
- Green Lantern, are you okay?
- This is a mistake.
We need to leave. We have to go!
Green Lantern, come back!
Now, surface dwellers,
feel the rage of Atlantis!
Well, I got the Gate working again.
- How'd you guys do?
- Not bad. Not bad at all.
Mount up! It is time to show them
what the Justice League can do!
Yeah!
So many eyes judging me,
everyone in the world watching me!
I can't handle this. I need help.
Oh, look, I can't do this alone!
Ring, show me all superheroes closest to me!
Whatever she's doing to them,
they can't last much longer.
Oh, this is the best!
No wonder Aquaman wanted to be King.
You get to do whatever you want!
You and I, Atrocitus,
are the unmatched rulers of this world!
I wouldn't be so sure of that, brother!
Impressive. But your pathetic machines
are no match for my Red Lantern rage!
You're all bark, and no bite!
Time for a cat nap!
Stop it!
You're supposed to be peaceful creatures.
There's nothing peaceful about you.
Your machines can't shield you
from my Lantern light forever.
Lighten up, Atrocitus.
Enough! You can't stop Atrocitus!
My central battery is full
from the rage of this planet,
and has rendered me all-powerful!
We have to destroy that battery.
Come on, team!
Brother, stop this madness now!
Never! I'm King!
My friends!
Ha-ha!
Where is your hope now?
Yeah, where's your hope?
I assume now, you'll try and take us
over with your Red Lantern rage.
All in good time, but right now,
you have a front row seat
to the destruction of your planet.
Yes! The destruction of...
- Say what now?
- Stage Three is ready.
Witness the power
of the Submerged, Limitless,
Underwater Rapid Pump!
The S-L-U-R-P? Slurp?
You must have tried really hard
to make that one work.
The SLURP takes in water,
vaporizing it into outer space,
until the world is left as dry as a desert.
A world without water, and it's all my fault!
But you said I would rule the oceans
and you would rule the dry land!
You didn't really think
I would share my kingdom
with a sniveling brat such as yourself?
Poor little Orm!
Always caught in your brother's shadow.
Never happy unless you had
a piece of everything he had.
Well, now, you can share in his failure.
You have the perfect seat from
which to watch the end of your world.
What? What do you think you're doing?
This isn't you, Mera!
- You have to fight it!
- Never!
In brightest day, in blackest night,
no evil shall escape my sight.
Let those who worship evil's might
beware my power, Green Lantern's light!
Where... Where am I?
- Mera, are you okay?
- Green Lantern?
What am I doing here? Where is Aquaman?
- That was amazing!
- But all those people watching...
How did you overcome your stage fright?
When I saw you two in trouble,
I stopped thinking
about myself and just reacted.
I'm very proud of you,
Green Lantern Jessica Cruz.
You have now unlocked
the mute option. Engage.
Funny. Now that I can, I don't want to.
I fear I am blushing.
- So is it over?
- Not quite. Look!
I really messed up.
Ormi, how can I help?
You still care, after all I've done to you?
Why?
Because like it or not, we are family.
And family has to stick together.
You're right. You've always been right.
I have so many regrets.
Me, too, brother. Me, too.
I just wish I was a better hero.
I know I'm not the flashiest
League member, or the greatest king.
I thought if I just faked it,
I would make it.
Instead, I've let everyone down.
That's the most ridiculous thing
I've ever heard.
That's kind of you to say,
but if I hadn't given up my crown,
none of this would be happening.
They would have found another way.
You are a great king, Aquaman,
and a great hero.
It was you that got us out of
the palace through the secret tunnels.
You helped us escape the smokestack
and led us to The Watering Hole.
You stood up to Lobo and got us back home.
The fact is, we've taken
you for granted, Aquaman.
If anyone can lead us to victory, you can.
You guys are the best.
Stand back!
The King of the Sea has work to do!
- Is he meditating?
- No. He's calling for help.
Huh?
What is that?
It looks like tiny, microscopic plankton.
Correct, Superman.
They are the key to our escape.
Thank you, my friends.
Let's do this!
Wait, if we got out there like this,
we'll be infected by the Red Lantern rage.
Let me handle that.
Excellent. My magic should safeguard us
from the effects of the Lantern.
Brilliant! Now, I'll handle Atrocitus.
You try to stop that machine.
- Are you sure?
- Don't worry. I've got his back.
- Together, brother?
- Together!
Okay. Try it now.
Argh! The shielding is too thick!
We're never gonna be able to do this.
We're gonna need a miracle.
Batman! The Justice League!
Oh! Beautiful sunshine.
I feel better already.
Oh! Am I ever glad to see you!
We're glad to see some
reinforcements up here.
Thanks to Green Lantern. Without her,
I'm afraid we'd be dead in the water.
Batman, where is Aquaman? Where is Arthur?
It is over, Atrocitus.
What?
Take this, you slimy oaf!
Brother!
No!
It's time to sleep with the fishes.
Poisedon's Trident!
For the one who is worthy!
Enough parlor tricks! Prepare for doom!
For Atlantis!
For the world!
No!
Huh?
Now it is finally over, Atrocitus!
For your world. Unfortunately for you,
the SLURP has already been activated,
and cannot be stopped.
All your precious water
is about to be sucked into oblivion.
There has to be a way to stop it.
If there is, I'm sure you could find it.
Go! I'll restrain Atrocitus.
You have a world to save, my King.
Ocean Master, let us...
I think we've heard enough from you!
This is Lois Lane reporting live from
above the water just outside Star City,
where a giant slurping device
is dropping the ocean's water level
at an incredible speed.
So far, the Justice League seem
to be unable to dismantle the device.
It's no good. Not even
my heat vision can penetrate it.
What are we gonna do?
I wish Arthur was here.
Arthur! You're okay!
I'm fine, Mera. It's good to see you.
I'm sorry for the things I said.
I didn't mean it.
No, Mera. I apologize.
I didn't think about how
losing the throne would affect you.
You're my wife, my queen.
We rule Atlantis together.
Now, I believe it's time to save the planet!
I share your sentiments, Aquaman.
Unfortunately, our weapons
are ineffective against this SLURP.
By themselves, perhaps,
but we can't give up yet.
If we concentrate everything we have
on a solitary point at the same time,
then maybe we have a chance. Who's with me?
I'm cheering for once. Hurray, or something.
Ready, Justice League?
Now!
- We moved it!
- Keep going! We can do this!
Fishy's right. We don't have enough power!
We need something more!
How about some more of the Main Man?
I'm back, baby!
Whoo!
I could never stay mad at you, Fishy!
Together!
- Yes! All right!
- We're not done yet!
It looks like the Justice League,
led by Aquaman,
have destroyed the device and saved the day!
She's right, you know.
You did lead us to victory.
I'd say it was more of a team effort.
My good citizens of Atlantis,
I have done you a great disservice
by saying the law prevents
Aquaman from being King.
In fact, the fine print was
something I put in there
with the help of a clerk named Sal
at an all-night copy center.
- There is no such law.
- Get off the stage!
And even if there were,
we can see he is worthy,
because he pulled the Trident
of Poseidon from the great statue.
So, Aquaman, my brother,
I give you back the crown
you so richly deserve.
Thank you...
Huzzah!
Thank you. I promise to be the
best king and the best hero I can be,
to Atlantis and the world!
Now, let us dance!
Wow. You Atlanteans really
know how to throw a party.
Thank you, Cyborg.
Well, I'm glad everything turned out okay.
But what are we gonna do about the
Red Lanterns, Dex-Starr and Atrocitus?
Leave them to me and Fishy.
Turns out Oa placed a bounty on their heads,
and I'm meaning to collect.
This isn't the last you've
heard of me. I'll be...
Ow!
No!
Thank you for your help, Lobo.
Yeah, but let's not get mushy.
Next time I see you yahoos,
I may not be on my best behavior.
So long, chumps!
Cyborg's mobile trouble alert!
It looks like Gorilla Grodd is attacking
the city of Kathmandu in Nepal.
Did someone say
high-altitude snowy mountains,
nowhere near any ocean or body of water?
That sounds like a job for Aquaman.
Call if you aren't going to be home
for supper.
Sure will. Well, what are we waiting for?
People need our help!
OK  杰西卡   振作起来   你行的
哈尔正在放假期间   而你也是个绿灯侠
他让你去正义大厅顶班  没什么大不了的
你很冷静   很镇定  很有控制力
冷静  很镇定 很有控制力    嗯?
闭嘴吧你   我可不记得哈尔的戒指和他说过话
那是因为绿灯侠乔丹已经积累了足够的绿光能量
来解锁静音按钮
戒指   启用静音模式
然而   你  绿灯侠杰西卡·克鲁兹    却没有
- 看来有麻烦了
- 哦   嗨   正义联盟
呃    我没碰它   我是说   我正要碰它
但我并没有没碰它   所以这不是我的错    我发誓
而且大家都看着我    所以我现在应该闭嘴
- 扣五个点绿光能量
- 为什么?
- 别找借口
- 别担心    绿灯侠
你没有做错什么    这是危险警报
- 它提醒我们当---
- 当有麻烦的时候?
是的   看到了吗？  你很有天分
露易丝·莱恩现场新闻
看来我们遇到真正的麻烦了
而且是以大写字母“L”为开头的家伙
露易丝有很多优点   蝙蝠侠     但我不会说她是个麻烦
不是露易丝  超人  你看
这是露易丝·莱恩     来自52区恐怖湖的报道
银河系赏金猎人暴狼正在横冲直撞
这简直就像是
大海捞针一样
现在已经废弃的52区设施
是为了简化军方复杂的机密外星科技部门
已经废弃？   我以为他们才刚建造好
简化程序反而使事情变得更加复杂
他们把所有的东西都搬到了新泽西州的一个新仓库里
你在哪里   你这个德比安星球的小混球?
暴狼    一个扎尼亚星人    超级强壮    超级强悍
还有满口脏话    他似乎在找什么东西
现在还不知道暴狼会发现什么危险的神器
我们得尽快赶到恐怖湖边
有人提到 "湖"字了吗?
为何听起来像是海王的工作!
海王   你应该知道恐怖湖并不是你的---
哇   对不起  下面的信号有点不稳定
到时候见   海王下线
显然   他并没有按我的要求建造海底信号塔
我们真的应该在这里建一个海底信号塔
信号响应太糟糕了   奥姆
我告诉过你  哥哥     我更喜欢被称为“海洋领主”
哦   对不起    海洋领主
别担心
你想叫什么我就叫你什么
哦    就是这个    水下飞机
我们刚好给你详细检查了一下，陛下
你们的工作也做得很棒
你们太棒了    我很喜欢当你们的国王
要把它开到满是灰尘的陆地上      我还真有点舍不得呢
不   不   不   去吧     陆地那儿需要你
你不在的时候   我会处理好这里的一切   再一次
噢！
谢谢  小奥姆
- 是"海洋领主"
- 好啦   好啦   好啦
虽然    你这个称号有点奇怪
因为毕竟我才是“七海之王”
但   呃    管它呢
我只是很高兴我们能从小争吵中走出来
努力帮助亚特兰蒂斯  不   帮助整个世界
同心协力
是的  我喜欢团队合作
告诉媚拉我会回家吃晚饭     当国王真好
是吗?    我们很快就会见到
干什么？  回去工作
好了   水下飞机   我们要去淡水区了
当正义联盟的朋友们遇到关于水方面的问题
需要我的帮助时    我感到非常欣慰
你在哪里?
你不可能永远躲着主角的
耶!
- OK   吉米   拍我
- 露易丝  这是个好主意吗？
普利策奖从来都不是靠好点子赢得的，吉米
快点    跟上
呃    这不是他们获奖的唯一原因吗？
暴狼      露易丝·莱恩     来自《星球日报》
啊   狗仔队
不    我是个严肃的记者
如果我是狗仔队
我就会批评你的衣着品味
- 太老土
- 什么?
女士   主角总是说  “黑色永远是最潮流的”
好吧    我说  主角马上就要感受到痛苦了    伙计
- 谁说的?
- 正义联盟说的
吉米    趴下
很高兴见到你   暴狼
我是海王   “七海之主”
“海豚保护者”   “亚特兰蒂斯国王”
- “飞机失事者”
-  “失事者”...
呃    我还不熟悉这个绰号
让我来搞定这个
再见了    你这个海底的乡巴佬
不    别这样     这些零件很重要
嘿    这是一驾定制的飞机    刚刚打过蜡
似乎海王是第一个
莫名其妙到达的正义联盟成员
尽管我们身处沙漠
呃    永别了   水下飞机  为了国王   你表现得很好
海王    我是《星球日报》的露易丝-莱恩
就像我们专业记者说的    你看起来真的很像
主角暴狼说的“把你的警告奉还给你”
不用担心   莱恩小姐
我要叫支援了  用我的心灵感应能力
召唤我的水族同胞   就在恐怖湖这里
但是   恐怖湖是一个干涸的湖床
好吧   那就有点难度了  是吧
那ABC几个计划---      不管了    我还是很强的
而且--- 啊?
噢     天哪
那一定很疼
天哪   莱恩小姐       海王真的快被撕成碎片了
不要打脸   不要打脸
走开   走开
救命
你不该这样对待王室
是吗？    痛得气喘吁吁的王室吗？
这就是为什么   人们从不让鱼去做人类的工作
- 吉米   告诉我你都拍下来了
- 完完全全
但万一暴狼要来抓我们呢?
不要惊慌    吉米     正义联盟来了
这是英雄的时刻
你们想让我当超级英雄   真的吗？
在整个正义联盟面前?    在大家的注视中？
来吧   绿灯侠   否则你会错过我们超级酷炫的出场方式
哦    谁会想错过这个呢
- 吉米  用慢镜头拍摄英雄登场
- 哦  好的
还有足够的时间来拍摄最精彩的戏分
现在投降吧  暴狼
在你的星球    你也许很强
但在地球金色太阳的照耀下  我才是最强的---
投降?  主角是永远不会投降的
我真的感觉到了
我们可能需要些帮助
啊!
我马上就出去了
暴狼就跟超人一样强?
- 天哪
- 你说得没错  铁皮人
你得更加努力才能搞定主角
也许蝙蝠侠可以用他可爱的小工具带里的东西阻止他
哦    不    她说出来了
哈
干嘛   你们懂的     他的万能腰带     很可爱的
你是说我的多功能腰带     对于各种各样的工具来说
这是一个方便的存储空间 而且不会碍事
像你说的可爱的小皮带能做到吗？
呃    有点
- 也许
- 你就是你  蝙蝠侠
- 我很抱歉  我只是想---
- 注意
如果我们想成功   那就必须团结协作
各位    数到三下就行动    一...
嗯    好吧     别等我了
- 二  ...
- 别再搞砸了
做个又大又强的东西
三
一个保险箱?   啊
噢    多勇敢啊    绿光能量再扣一分
哈    小孩子的把戏
嘿     继续摇晃你的鱼鳍吧  水母先生
呃     水母实际上没有鳍
介意我带你去兜风吗?
超人    钢骨    快
嘿   啊   所以   这就是你一直躲藏的地方
来爸爸这
- 演出结束了  对吧?
- 最好是这样
我们都使出了浑身解数来对付他了
如果这就是你们全部的本事    那你们最好再加点油了
不可能    他身上一点划痕都没有
绿灯     用你的全部能量打他
呃   OK
我做到了
我并没有做到
我很想留下来继续玩      但我已经得到了我想要的
再见    废物联盟 !
快   别让他逃了
耶      哈哈哈
- 逃得好
- 你们认为他来这里是为了什么?
我不知道      但不管是什么    都不可能是好事
嗯   有谁看到海王了吗?
- 帮个小忙     拜托
- 别担心    我来救你
谢谢  小伙伴们   很高兴你们来了  我们真的挽救了局面
我说的对吗?
- 露易丝·莱恩  《星球日报》的
- 是的    我知道
被暴狼羞辱是什么感觉？
再加上被正义联盟再一次拯救呢？
我是团队的一员    正义联盟的胜利就是我的胜利
所以    你不介意全世界都看到
亚特兰提斯的国王    像一条受惊的鱼一样逃离暴狼?
不   你这样说对鱼是不公平的
- 而且    呃    我并没有逃跑
- 露易丝      恕我冒昧
海王是正义联盟的重要成员
- 重要在哪方面?
- 现在    好吧    他...   呃...
- 他     呃 ...
- 别看着我   我是新来的
海王与海洋生物对话的能力是一项至关重要的技能
我相信他会非常有效地使用它
在将来的某个时候     在有必要的时候
好了   女士们先生们
海王的队友100%支持他
即使他的技能过于边缘化
《星球日报》 露易丝·莱恩播报完毕
咔  大新闻    我们回去吧  今晚七点准时播出
我不会担心的   海王
现在没有多少人看网络新闻了
哦   我不担心
此外  亚特兰蒂斯没有有线电视
我只是很高兴我们终于聚在一起了
我们找个地方痛痛快快地庆祝一下怎么样？
或者  或者  或者我们首先要弄清楚为什么暴狼会在这里
没有什么比苹果派更值得用来做庆祝食物的了
我能做出连上帝吃了都感动到哭的美味大餐
让我们去吃大肚汉堡吧
请允许我诚挚地邀请你们大家来亚特兰蒂斯
我们将在哪里庆祝我当七海之王的周年纪念日
我们要去亚特兰蒂斯了    这真是太棒了
海底自驾游   我爱大海
友好的鱼  和平的海豚  没有人看着你
加5点绿光能量  奖励你做出了适合的交通工具   干得好
啊   大海
已知的  最有趣的   水中生物的家园
除了你们     我是说---
哇    好多鱼
是的  鱼  植物   我们这里什么都有
有冰冻酸奶吗?
没有   它们会在海水中融化   但是我们有五颜六色的岩石
还有   呃   呃 ... 珊瑚     我们还有珊瑚
珊瑚和岩石不是一回事吗?
差远了
这是我吗？还是水在变颜色?
好眼力  钢骨    红色和黄色波长的光
只能在水下走这么远
这就是为什么在这么深的地方所有的东西看起来都是蓝色和绿色的
喔    难怪   没有阳光让我感觉有点绿绿的
我们亚特兰蒂斯有治疗你晕船的方法
太美丽了
那是什么声音?
哦  抱歉   听起来像唱歌
哦   那一定是欢迎我回来的歌声
我的人民总是喜欢在我回家的时候唱小曲
亚特兰蒂斯人真的是地球上最善良的人   嘘    听
我们的国王 七海之王
最强大的英雄是他
他一边游泳一边战斗
没有比他更伟大的英雄了!
鲨鱼  鲸鱼  风暴  都不是    最强大的英雄是他
他一边游泳一边战斗
他就是海洋之王   海洋之王就是他
- 他们真的很爱你  海王
- 谁不爱呢?
那个家伙是谁?  看起来很伟大
波塞冬国王
他手里拿着神秘的希望之戟
传说中   无论谁从雕像手中拔出三叉戟
就能当亚特兰蒂斯的合法统治者
- 就像亚瑟王的神剑
- 什么神剑?
有人做到了吗？
不  这只是一个老掉牙的传说
虽然可以经常看到有小孩试图把它拔出来
瞧
- 我快就成功了 这是我的
- 你能行的  你能行的
我们到了
呃   问题是  我们在这下面怎么呼吸
我发明了一种特殊的蝙蝠水喷雾
能暂时氧化我们周围的水
哦  你在那些可爱的小袋子里放了喷雾
欢迎光临   请不要客气
就像我在墨西哥湾的海豚朋友说的那样...
大致翻译过来的是 ：“ 咪 卡萨 艾斯  苏 卡瑟 ”
亚瑟   你终于回来了
媚拉   见到真是太高兴了
- 那个高个子美女是谁?
- 高个子?
我们乐高人不是都一样大小的吗？ 钢骨
这是我妻子  媚拉
等等  你结婚了?
我是说    当然    你结婚了     海王经常在说到你
嗯   很抱歉我一直没有机会跟大家见面
亚瑟不在时 我一直忙着完善我的手艺
- 你的手艺?
- 是的
媚拉不仅是亚特兰蒂斯的王后
她还是个硬水魔法大师
- 哦    先做条鱼
- 硬水?
- 就像水果硬糖那样吗?
- 哦  不 不  更厉害
看这个 媚拉 做条鱼
是不是很神奇？
哦   我的上帝  你是怎么做到的?
魔法   有了我的水系魔法  我可以变任何东西
- 这是辆车
- 再做条鱼
- 还有椅子
- 鱼
你的鱼又来了  亚瑟
鱼  我每次都受不了
我很高兴你们都在这里
正好赶上为亚瑟举行的皇家宴会
请跟我一起参加
王座厅的宴会
好的!
用餐时间到    是时候考验一下我的铁胃了
王座大厅？你坐在宝座上？
哈    没什么大不了的
哦  天哪    我敢打赌这里的海鲜一定是最好的
说得没错    钢骨
亚特兰蒂斯是海洋的烹饪中心
我相信你会喜欢的
今晚   我们将为您提供海苔汉堡
海藻意大利面和海藻沙拉
海藻?  龙虾和螃蟹呢?
或者来点虾米?
当然不行
在海底   所有的海洋生物都有充分的公民权利
但别担心  试试海藻沙拉
味道就像 糯 糯 糯 米
吃进 小 肚 肚 肚 里
哦   天哪    我真的很想吃龙虾
我的错
还有人听到什么了吗?
或者是我的超级听力有问题?
蝙蝠打嗝！不好意思        声音是从外面传来的
都过来     都过来     靠近点  靠近点
这真的太过分了!
这种情况会持续多久?
也许他这次会用什么东西让我们大吃一惊
上次 他讲了三个小时    我还要给船打蜡呢
我来讨论一件非常重要的事情的
亚特兰蒂斯的命运!
- 海洋领主
- 谁是海洋领主?
七大洋中最咸的坏蛋
他也是我异父同母的半个兄弟
一旦你了解他   他真的没那么坏    来吧!
海洋领主是海王的亲戚?
我不记得他在申请表上写过
现在我必须更新他的档案记录了
你们说我们的国王很强大，但在陆地上
他只不过是一个笑话
我在这里看到的  唯一的笑话  正在舞台上
真的吗?   我来问你们
如果国王不能打败陆地居民
那他怎么能保护海洋中的你们  嗯？
我不知道   他总是对我们很好
是吗?
请让我向我们敬爱的国王透露一些情况
警告
啊
绿灯侠  你在干什么?
戒指自动反应的
侦测到愤怒值的增加
那是什么?  发生了什么事?
就像我说的我们消失的国王...
消失的国王...
你怎么能追随一个人人都嘲笑的国王呢? 看
胆小鬼     只会逃
胆小鬼?
正义联盟出现之前 是我一直在苦苦支撑大局!
最后  你怎么能相信一个
只有半个亚特兰提斯血统的国王呢？
是的  我父亲是一个普通的陆地居民
我必须重新更新他的档案文件
- 他不能当国王
- 啊   这改变了一切
海洋领主  兄弟  这是什么意思?
这是我当年把你锁在浴室里的报复吗
我们进去谈谈吧
没什么可谈的   是时候采取行动了
你违反亚特兰蒂斯的法律太久了
法律?  亚瑟  他在说什么?
我证明给你看   你确实不应该成为国王
看   亚特兰蒂斯宪法
- 这能证明什么?
- 在那里  接近底部那里 那一行小字
在这  让我用我的超级视力看看
哇    那个   太小了
我可能需要一个放大镜才行
我的多功能腰带还有另一个优点
让我们来看看  这上面说
"要统治亚特兰蒂斯  你必须是血统纯正的亚特兰蒂斯人"
不   不
我无法呼吸了!
但你可以在任何地方呼吸
哦  说得对
所以  你瞧  兄弟  你不是合法的统治者
我才是
海洋领主!  海洋领主!
亚瑟  你打算怎么办？
我只能做一件事
根据我已经宣誓效忠的亚特兰提斯法律
在此 我把王冠让给我的兄弟
半个兄弟
好好统治吧 我的国王
别想拿回去
海洋领主!  海洋领主!  海洋领主!
亚瑟   真不敢相信你把王位让给别人了
媚拉  我已经做了决定
甚至没跟我商量   我们不应该是一个队的吗？亚瑟
- 媚拉  我---
- 不
这就是你想要的  好吧   没有我你也无所谓
哇   这一招真的好酷     她真的好厉害
太快了?   我的错
现在我是亚特兰蒂斯的国王
让我把你们介绍给那个鼓励我拿走我该得的东西的人
威胁警报！检测到欧米茄能量
喔    不
我的皇家顾问
还有全能的好人
阿托希塔斯
执行防御策略  欧米茄五级戒备
这是你的防御策略?
一个沙发什么也做不了!
啊
谁是阿托希塔斯?
阿托希塔斯  红灯军团的首领
他们能用愤怒的力量控制心灵
我建议快点离开
哈尔曾提到过红灯军团
他们用红灯的愤怒能量  感染了亚特兰蒂斯人
看来是绿灯侠的防护罩  在保护我们不受红灯的伤害
你们好  水下居民们
作为你们的新皇家顾问
我的第一条建议是
消灭正义联盟
- 摧毁他们!
- 抓住他们!  抓住他们!
这个穿披风的是我的!
快滚出来!
我不知道我的防护罩还能撑多久
快撑不住了
不知怎么的  我觉得出去揍他们是不对的
不能这么做  我虽然已经不是他们的国王了   但他们仍然是我的子民
我们必须撤退  然后制定一个计划
我知道一条出路  但我们需要分散他们的注意力
幸运的是  我的超级实用腰带正好有这个东西
墨水炸弹  太巧妙了
你看到他们去哪儿了吗?    他们去了哪里？
找到他们     他们不可能走得太远
你做得很好 海洋领主
你的意思是“海洋领主大王”
是的  当然了  陛下
我用红灯的愤怒力量
感染亚特兰蒂斯人的计划似乎奏效了
最后  整个亚特兰蒂斯终将臣服于我
现在开始第二阶段
这些秘密通道只有王室才知道
如果我们迅速采取行动  也许能在被发现之前逃出去
怎么逃?  我相信他们已经把王宫包围起来了
- 海之门   当然了
- “海”什么?
看啊
那是什么?
那就是海之门
它可以打开一个跨维度通道
能沟通亚特兰蒂斯和其他有水的行星
哦  我不知道亚特兰蒂斯的科技竟如此先进
更新档案文件
我想他们在这下面
海王    你一定能做点什么
嗯  我不知道怎么切换定位
但我可以打开它最后一个去过的地方
- 让我们行动起来 小伙伴们
- 你们先走   我留下来关门
我不能丢下我的人民  留在这个可怕的困境中  还有媚拉
如果你现在不来   你就没办法拯救你的人民了
杰西卡   快点   他们来了
但这会通向哪里呢?  如果那边有更多的人
望着我指指点点呢?
这种可能性大约是17亿分之1
所以  你是说有这种可能?
绿灯  没时间了想这想那了  快点
他们在那里
等等  不要
我是说 "不要"       不是说 "甜甜圈"
扣五点绿光能量  因为发音不清楚
他们逃脱了   通知阿托希塔斯
- 在这里!
威胁逼近
我好像听到什么了
真是谢谢了   你这个大嘴巴
快点  远离你的麻烦 这似乎有所帮助
死路一条   哦  不    我该怎么办？
是的  如果你拥有宇宙中最强大的武器就好了...
哦   等等...
拜托  戒指  帮个忙怎么样？
你必须克服你的恐惧
- 我不行
- 你行的
我挑选新兵的记录一直很完美  直到现在
好吧  祝下一位候选人好运
哇
搞定了
从我自己的王国逃跑
- 无法容忍
- 我们在哪?
看起来像某种工厂  但是他们在做什么?
更重要的是  绿灯侠在哪里？
不幸的是  这次危机证明她经验不足
她有点太嫩了  我们得回去找她
海王   你能把海之门重新打开吗？
重新打开?
有人来了   大家快躲起来
好吧     真奇怪    我应该能听到他们走近的
- 武装入侵?
- 那是什么？ 海王
好吧    神奇女侠  我能和海洋生物交流
但我也会说一点猫的话
他们正在为入侵做准备     或者猫砂什么的
- 不论发生哪一种情况
- 当然了
那是灵星    红灯猫
现在一切都很清楚了
阿托希塔斯和海洋领主在亚特兰蒂斯使用海之门
将一支由愤怒驱动的战斗机器组成的舰队带到地球上
不可能的     海之门的设计初衷并不是为了运送军队
这将需要更强大的能量
说到能量
我发现一个巨大的能量波从这个房间的某个地方涌来
- 就像那样
- 来自52区的球体
这就是驱动海之门的能量
现在阿托希塔斯可以利用亚特兰蒂斯作为滩头阵地来攻击陆地世界
太过分了  他们拿走了我的王冠
我的王国    现在   还要打破
我的两个家乡之间的和平
我必须回去
这些机器人挡在我们和海之门中间
我们怎么过去？
这看起来像是超人该做的工作
我不明白你的意思    我的超能力消失了
以后再担心吧   超人    他们来了
这是我的万能腰带的另一个方便的工具
哦
他们一定有自动修理系统
钢骨    你能打乱他们吗？
捂住你们的耳朵     现在是声波加农炮时间
噢    天啊!
你这个哈迪斯的毛球     真是一只狂暴的猫科动物
OK   克拉克    你能行的
神奇女侠     你还好吗?
但是   妈妈   其他孩子的飞机都不是隐形的啊
显然    神奇女侠被打傻了
- 你确定吗?
- 哔-吧-吧-吧-吧 !
是的  我很确定
哦    你好
你是一只太空海豚  是吧
是的   我知道你们的种族
让我用心灵感应来请你的帮忙
什么?   我永远不会说你母亲的事
我的心灵感应对太空海豚不起作用
这是一只愤怒的太空海豚
我们完全不是对手
- 我们得离开这里
- 那就交给我吧
这应该能给我们争取点时间
- 太神了!
- 在这里!
哈  看来你进不去了
哈哈   没错   但它为什么在笑?
哇   大家不觉得这里很热吗?
我以为只有我觉得热     我都快着火了!
着火...
难怪这个房间装饰得像火炉一样...
因为它就是一个火炉
一个火炉   我们该怎么办?    我们得快点离开这里
没有超能力   我就不能带大家飞出去
而且我的火箭靴还进水短路了
我的头脑开始清醒了  我要做的就是...
看来我的钩索也勾不到烟囱的顶端
我喜欢奶酪    但它不喜欢我
是的   无论如何   我们只要像水母一样
蝙蝠侠   你的万能腰带里有蝙降落伞吧
那儿      原理很简单
热量上升   我们也会跟着上升
- 起作用了
- 但还不够    看啊 !
我不知道我们能不能撑过去
我们成功了     嘿
你不是说海之门能通向其他有水的星球吗?
本来应该是这样的
这外面和火炉里面一样热
我把你们带到哪里了?   死亡谷吗?
离死亡不远了
看 !     红太阳
难怪我的超能力不管用了    我们在另一个星球上
没有社会文明的话    我们在这里撑不了多久的
你是怎么把降落伞绑在腰带上的?
这是蝙蝠秘密    快    走吧
等我回到家的时候   我也要做一条多功能腰带
媚拉     谢天谢地     你怎么找到我的？
我听到你的声音从隧道的另一端传来
看看我发现了什么
有人偷偷在我的王国里集结了一支舰队
这里有大量的武器让阿托希塔斯来侵略陆地世界
- 我们得告诉大家
- 为什么?
陆地世界给我们带来的只有麻烦
- 他们应该被毁灭
- 但海王曾说---
我的丈夫吗?  他甚至没有勇气为自己的王位而战
试着对她讲点道理看看
媚拉    你必须对抗它
我宁愿对抗你
强烈建议采取战术撤退
也许你们这些陆地居民应该被消灭
就从你开始!
住手!    我是说   退后
你认为亚特兰蒂斯王后会害怕
你这个海里的弱鸡吗?
哈    你没打中
我不是瞄准你的
啊    啊
聪明    加10点绿光能量
希望哈尔的飞行课能有点用
嘿    伙计们    只有我觉得   还是这沙子太软了
我们就像在水上行走    是的   水
是水    看啊    有水
下来吧   伙计们     这水真太完美了
事情发生得比我想象的要快
缺水使他产生了幻觉
我觉得不舒服
退后一步
让我用蝙蝠嗅盐试着救活他
你的多功能腰带几乎和你一样神奇
差不多吧   现在    退后
他僵硬得像块木板
即使我恢复超能力   我想我也搬不动他
让我试试
真有意思
- 啥意思?
- 神奇女侠   你能把他举起来吗?
奇怪的是    他的身体好像在向什么东西靠近
如果要我猜的话     我想是他的亚特兰蒂斯生理机能
让他自然地被水吸引
他就是个人体探测器
那么   我们该怎么办？
跟着他走
啊   媚拉
汪   汪    退下   狗东西     我是亚特兰蒂斯王后
是前王后
哦    关于王后退位的事    抱歉    才怪
但现在   你已经看到了我领导的能力
你想怎么为我效劳?  嗯
那些住在地面上的家伙   他们真把我惹火了
- 听你这么说我很高兴
- 如果可以的话   陛下
我们第二阶段进展得很完美
按照我们双方的互利安排
去吧   为你的新主人   拿下陆地世界
陆地世界和海王    会感受到我的愤怒的
- 我喜欢星城码头
- 多过你爱我吗?
-不好玩吗？达米安
- 哼
哦   拜托    不会那么糟吧
芭芭拉   我们只是在绕圈子
我不知道这有什么可兴奋的
这就是为什么要放一天假   不当蝙蝠女和罗宾了
你需要学习怎样当一个普通的小孩
我是个普通的孩子啊   我也会做小孩子的事
比如呢?  你不玩电子游戏  也不熬夜
你说话的样子都不像个孩子
- 我像
- 不像   你在做什么?
访问蝙蝠数据库      搜索“孩子的行为”
快速阅读    完成
你想让我表现得像个孩子    没问题
图腾召唤   触发击杀
- 啊?
- 放松一下  小芭
这一定会从G到双O D
哦     看我都做了什么?
自拍
让我颤抖吧    我已经钓到一条大鱼了
那是什么鱼?
真想知道它煎起来是什么味道
尝起来像愤怒的味道
看来我们的休息日被取消了
罗宾?  你在听我说话吗？
- 小孩子不听话
- 啊   别闹了
坚持住   伙计们
我们到了山顶上 就休息一下
哦   不    我开始产生幻觉了
你没有幻觉 超人    我也看见了
“水坑酒吧”  这地方的名字真有趣
你觉得我们应该进去看看吗？
哇
神奇女侠
哦
- 你要点什么?
- 请给我五杯水
五杯水?  你们肯定不是本地人
让我看看能帮你们拿些什么
- 啊
- 欧 耶
可爱的海马啊    这是我喝过的最好的水
- 我要再来一杯
- 真是土豪啊
- 这可是很贵的
- 水很贵吗？
自从那个红家伙把所有的水都吸了出来之后  是的
阿托希塔斯来过这?
如果他把这个星球上所有的水都拿走了     那---
他可能也会对地球做同样的事    我们必须回去阻止他
话说   你们这些人是怎么付钱的?
呃...
把帐记在我的蝙蝠信用卡上
不收信用卡    只收克拉托币
克拉托币是什么?
先生    我们必须在这附近做点什么来付清我们的账单
你唯一能做的就是付钱   否则
否则什么?      我已经失去了一切
我妻子生我的气
全世界都认为我是个笑柄
你和我可以成为朋友     敬朋友
- 海王没事吧?
- 海王明显已经脱水了
身体缺水显然影响他的心情
你影响了我的脾气   蝙蝠侠
你们都是
赖账不给？ 哈
那好   我想这意味着我得把你们介绍给我的讨债人
海王    你看---
不     挽救一个尴尬的聚会 唯一的办法
是邀请更多的伙伴参与进来
哦     对哦    等等   啊
你们知道的   曾经我可以付清所有这些水的钱
真见鬼     我甚至可以买下这整个地方  但是不行
我不得不放弃我的王冠
我只是鞠了个躬   让海洋领主把我头上的王冠摘下来
我是说    当国王压力很大   你们知道吗？
相信我    在海底每平方英寸有8吨重
我知道压力   我曾经是国王
发生什么事了?
好像是本地人
在帮我们付账
太好了
哇    海王    太棒了     我是说    有什么是你做不到的吗
约德尔唱法
我的鳃和舌头不知道该怎么配合才好
鼓掌欢迎主角登场
我该怎么阻止这个怪物东西?
- 第一步    停止尖叫
- 噢   完了
嗷！  嗷！  嗷！
逃脱成功安全着陆... 对吧?
正确   再加上两点绿光能量
才两点      真小气
绿灯侠
蝙蝠女     罗宾     你们在这里干什么?
给小孩子五分   老蝙蝠零分
我们希望能休息一天
但现在     海王的亚特兰蒂斯军队正在进攻
什么     不   不
亚特兰蒂斯人被阿托希塔斯和他的愤怒之光控制着
我们得离开这里去找其他英雄
没有时间了    看
摧毁陆地居民   攻击   攻击
哟    看这都有谁呀  上次我见到你们的时候
我让你们的朋友出尽了洋相
我赚的过最容易的钱
钱?    有人雇你来做这事吗?
是啊     有个叫水坑王子的人
或者是叫湖泊领袖---
海洋领主
是的   就是这家伙     他让我去拿能量球
然后在这个过程中羞辱一下这条咸鱼
就是这个球给红灯军团的海之门提供了动力
好吧   不管你是不是被雇用的   偷窃就是偷窃
恐怕我们得逮捕你
喔    别搞错状况   我不是来打架的
我在找我的朋友  太空海豚
你们不会碰巧看见我的朋友吧
我认识它
而且我知道他在哪里
那你现在就告诉我
有一个条件
你疯了吗？  告诉他
唯一的条件是
如果你不告诉我     我就把你捣成鱼酱
那就来呀   我没什么可失去的了
但是你永远也找不到你的朋友太空海豚了
嗯
水母先生毕竟还是有骨气的
你想要什么?
我们要你带我们去红灯工厂
想办法用海之门带我们回家
一言为定   要么接受  要么放弃
好吧
成交
看起来亚特兰蒂斯的国王回来了
酒保   我再拿一杯水上路
对不起   伙计   最后一点水都被你们喝光了
最后一点水?  别傻了
我可是人体探测器      我知道水在哪里
为什么     你的酒吧下面就有一个蓄水池
好吧     我们走吧
我的摩托车上只能再坐一个人
你们其他人怎么去呢
我有个主意
真是太棒了
- 感觉我又能飞了
- 比我的隐形飞机还要平稳
这有点好笑
蝙蝠翻转
入侵进行得很顺利
他们就像是嘴巴呼吸不到空气了
因为亚特兰蒂斯战舰让他们尝到了被污染的味道
没有什么能阻止我们   向地球29%的人类
夺回属于我们100%的资源
加快速度   朋友们
给我们带个大的战利品来挂在王座上吧
我喜欢这个节目
现在   开始第三阶段
等等   我们只谈了两个阶段
- 第三阶段是---
- 哦    我还没跟你说吗?
我正在用亚特兰蒂斯人帮我组装新武器
它将平息地面上的任何抵抗
呜    听起来真不错   它是做什么的？
你很快就会明白的
此外   国王不必为陆地上的事情操心
这就是我们达成的协议
我统治海洋世界   而你统治陆地世界
- 好吧    继续工作
- 如你所愿
就像我们承诺的那样   暴狼先生      你的朋友在那里
太空海豚
令人惊讶的因素就这么多了
- 为正义而战
- 等我一下
有没有梯子    或者…    哦    好吧
回来  你们这些铁皮盒子
工厂机器人吗?     试一下我这先进机器人的威力
你最好企求我是个爱狗人士
太空海豚      我真的好担心你
你不见了    我不知道你去了哪里
能量球肯定为整个设施提供电力
快点    大门正在关闭
好了    我来了   为了正义而...
呃    大门已经关上了
我不敢相信太空海豚会那样做    他戳了我的眼睛
- 还用他的尾巴打你
- 还用他的尾巴打我
别帮倒忙   钢骨
听着      听着
友谊的小船  就像任何珍贵的东西一样    是值得为之奋斗的
跟我们来   帮我们解救太空海豚
还有那些在红灯军团控制下的人
不   不
主角不会爬回去乞求成为任何人的朋友
- 但---
- 不   这是你的战斗
我不干了     我不需要任何朋友    我什么都不需要
我可没想到会是这样
我们得回去和阿托希塔斯的军队作战
但怎么回?
嗯   我有个主意
嘿   我的热狗   噢
哇
我们在对抗整个军队    打倒强权
我喜欢这种热情
苍蝇拍
我知道    我知道   这不是苍蝇拍    别怪我
我是露易丝·莱恩，现场报道
随着正义联盟其他成员的消失
唯一能抵御入侵的
只有罗宾、蝙蝠女和新绿灯侠
全世界都在关注他们是否能成功
全世界   都在看着……这是太疯狂了
- 绿灯侠   你还好吧?
- 这是个错误
我们必须离开  我们得走了
绿灯侠    回来
现在   陆地居民们   感受亚特兰蒂斯的愤怒吧
好吧   我让海之门又恢复工作了
- 伙计们怎么样?
- 还不赖   一点都不赖
加油     是时候让他们见识一下正义联盟的厉害了
耶
有那么多的眼睛在评判我   世界上的每一个人都在看着我
我应付不了这个  我需要帮助
哦   瞧   我一个人做不到
戒指    让我看看最近的超级英雄在哪里
不管她对他们做了什么   他们都撑不了多久了
哦   这就是最好的
难怪海王想当国王     你想做什么就做什么
你和我  阿托希塔斯    是这个世界上无与伦比的统治者
我可不敢那么肯定    兄弟！
不错嘛   但你们可怜的机器
不是我的红灯怒火的对手
你只会叫   不会咬人
该小睡一会儿了
住手
你应该是爱好和平的动物啊
可你一点也不平静
你的机器无法永远挡住我的红灯
放轻松,   阿托希塔斯
够了     你们是无法阻止阿托希塔斯的
我的中央电池充满了来自这个星球的愤怒
让我无所不能
我们必须摧毁那个电池    快点     小伙伴们
兄弟    别再胡闹了
决不，我才是大王
朋友们
哈---哈
现在 你的希望在哪里?
是啊    你的希望在哪里？
我猜现在你会用红灯愤怒来控制我们
一切都很顺利    但现在
你们可以坐在前排观看地球的毁灭
是的     地球的毁灭...
- 你在说什么?
- 第三阶段准备好了
见证 这来自
深埋在海底的无限的超级水泵的力量吧
字母S-L-U-R-P ? 吞噬?
你一定是想了破头才想出这个称号吧
吞噬机抽水   把水蒸发到太空中
直到世界变得像沙漠一样干燥
一个没有水的世界  这都是我的错
但你说过  让我统治海洋   你来统治陆地
你不会真的以为我会跟你分享我的王国吧
和你这个爱哭鬼?
可怜的小奥姆
总是被你哥哥的阴影所笼罩
除非你拥有他的一切  否则你永远不会快乐
好了   现在   你可以分享他的失败了
你们现在已经有了完美的座位 来观看世界末日了
什么?   你以为你在干什么?
这不是你   媚拉
- 你必须反抗
- 绝不
在最亮的白天  在最黑的夜晚
任何邪恶都逃不过我的视线
让那些崇拜邪恶力量的人
畏惧我的力量   绿灯侠的光芒
哪里 ...    我这是在哪里?
- 媚拉    你还好吧?
- 绿灯侠
我在这里做什么?     海王在哪里?
- 这真是太神奇了
- 可所有的人都在看着 ...
你是怎么克服怯场的?
当我看到你们俩有麻烦的时候
我就不再考虑自己了    我要行动起来
我真为你骄傲   绿灯侠杰西卡·克鲁兹
您现在已经解锁了静音模式  请用
有意思    现在我可以了  但我反而不想要
恐怕我都脸红了
- 所以 结束了吗?
- 不完全是    看
我真的搞砸了
奥米     要我怎么帮忙?
我对你那么过分   你还在乎我
为什么?
因为不管你喜不喜欢   我们都是一家人
一家人必须团结在一起
你是对的    你总是对的
我感到非常后悔
我也是     弟弟     我也是
我只希望我是个更强的英雄
我知道我不是最耀眼的联盟队员    也不是最伟大的国王
我以为只要装作不在乎   我就能做得到
相反    我让所有人都失望了
那是我听过的最可笑的事
你说的对    但是如果我没有放弃王位的话
所有的这一切这些都不会发生
他们还是会找到别的方法得逞的
你是一位伟大的国王     海王    也是一位伟大的英雄
是你让我们通过秘密隧道离开了宫殿
你帮我们逃出烟囱    把我们带到了水坑酒吧
你反抗暴狼    带我们回家
事实上    我们认为你是理所当然的    海王
如果有人能带领我们走向胜利    那一定是你
你们是最棒的
退后      海洋之王还有工作要做
- 他是在沉思吗？
- 不   他正在呼叫支援
啊?
那是什么?
看起来像微小的浮游生物
没错   超人      它们是我们逃跑的关键（钥匙）
谢谢你们    我的朋友们
放手一搏吧
等等    如果我们像这样出去
我们会被红灯能量的愤怒感染
让我来处理
太好了       我的魔法可以保护我们不受红灯的影响
精彩   现在   我来处理阿托希塔斯      你们去阻止那台机器
- 你确定吗?
- 别担心    我支持他
- 一起上   兄弟
- 一起上
OK    现在试试看
啊      防护罩太厚了
我们永远也做不到这一点    我们需要奇迹
蝙蝠侠    正义联盟
哦        美丽的阳光         我已经感觉好多了
噢       我从没那么高兴地见到你们
我们很高兴看到这里有增援部队
多亏了绿灯侠   没有她的话      恐怕我们已经死在水里了
蝙蝠侠     海王在哪里?      亚瑟在哪里？
结束了     阿托希塔斯
什么?
尝尝这个     你这个粘糊糊的笨蛋
弟弟
- 不
是时候和你的鱼一起沉睡了
波塞冬的三叉戟
为了那个有资格的人
别耍花招了    准备迎接末日吧!
为了亚特兰蒂斯
为了世界
不
现在    终于结束了     阿托希塔斯
对你的世界来说是的   不幸的是对你来说
吞噬机已经激活  无法停止
你们所有宝贵的水都将被吸干
一定有办法地能阻止它的
如果有   我相信你会找到的      去吧    我来看住阿托希塔斯
你有一整个世界要去拯救   我的国王
海洋领主   让我们---
我想你说的已经够多了
我是露易丝·莱恩     在星城外的水上进行现场报道
一个巨大的吸管正在快速抽水
海平面一直在以惊人的速度下降
到目前为止    正义联盟似乎无法拆除这个装置
不太妙    就连我的热视线都无法穿透它
我们该怎么办?
我希望亚瑟在这里
亚瑟    你没事了
我很好    媚拉    很高兴见到你
我为我说过的话感到抱歉     我真的不是那个意思
不    媚拉     我才要道歉
我没想到失去王位会对你有什么影响
你是我的妻子   我的王后       我们一起统治亚特兰蒂斯
现在   我想是时候拯救这个星球了
我同意你的看法    海王
不幸的是      我们的武器对吞噬机无效
各自出招也许行不通     但我们不能放弃
如果我们同时把所有的力量都集中在一个点上
也许我们还有机会赢        谁想跟我来？
我只欢呼一次     万岁    还有    那啥的---
准备好了吗     正义联盟?
上
- 已经动了
- 继续加油    我们能行的
太空海豚说得对
我们的力量还不够
我们需要更多力量
再加上主角的力量怎么样?
我回来了    宝贝
喔
我再也不生你的气了 太空海豚
一起上
- 耶    太好了
- 我们还没完事呢
看起来正义联盟在海王的带领下
摧毁了这个装置并拯救了全世界
她说得对
你确实带领我们走向了胜利
我认为这更多的是团队合作
亚特兰蒂斯的好公民们
我给你造成了很大的伤害
我说过法律不允许海王成为国王
事实上   这一条是我乱写进去的
在复印中心一个叫萨尔的职员的帮助下印上去的
- 其实根本没有这样的法律
- 下台去吧!
即使有   我们也能看出他是最有资格的
因为他把海神的三叉戟从巨大的雕像上拔出来了
所以    海王   我的哥哥
我把你应得的王冠还给你
谢谢你
好哇
谢谢你    我保证一定会成为最好的国王   成为最好的英雄
为了亚特兰蒂斯和全世界
现在     让我们一起跳舞吧
喔    你们亚特兰蒂斯人真会开派对
谢谢你    钢骨
我很高兴一切都好起来了
但是我们要怎么处理红灯、 灵星 和阿托希塔斯呢？
把它们留给我和太空海豚吧
欧亚星正悬赏 他们
而我正好想去领赏
这肯定不是你们最后一次见到我    我一定会---
噢
不
谢谢你的帮助    暴狼
是啊   但少跟我玩多愁善感那一套
下次再见到你们    我可能就没那么好说话了
再见了   傻瓜们
钢骨的自动警报响了
看起来像是大猩猩古鲁德在攻击
尼泊尔首都加德满都市
有人说高海拔的雪山
离海洋和水域都很远吗？
这听起来就像是海王的工作
如果你不回家吃晚饭，就打电话来
一定会的       那么    我们还在等什么?
有人需要我们的帮助